{
    "subject": "resource/Here_Comes_the_Navy",
    "predicate": "ontology/starring",
    "object": "resource/James_Cagney",
    "human_readable": "The movie 'Here Comes the Navy' stars James Cagney.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8318139910697937,
            "question": "Who starred in the movie 'Here Comes the Navy'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.805903971195221,
            "question": "What is the name of the movie starring James Cagney?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7114573121070862,
            "question": "Who directed the movie 'Here Comes the Navy'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6200383901596069,
            "question": "What other actors appeared in the movie 'Here Comes the Navy'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6087456941604614,
            "question": "What are some common themes in movies starring James Cagney?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5640168786048889,
            "question": "When was the movie 'Here Comes the Navy' released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5109429955482483,
            "question": "What genre is the movie 'Here Comes the Navy' likely to be?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4911231994628906,
            "question": "Is James Cagney known for any other movies?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4603434205055237,
            "question": "How popular was the movie 'Here Comes the Navy' upon its release?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4089195430278778,
            "question": "Is there a particular historical context surrounding the making of 'Here Comes the Navy'?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The movie 'Here Comes the Navy' stars James Cagney.",
            "html": "dbpedia_6691_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How popular was the movie 'Here Comes the Navy' upon its release?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6691_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is James Cagney known for any other movies?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6691_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What genre is the movie 'Here Comes the Navy' likely to be?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6691_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6691_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6691_38.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6691_39.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6691_41.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6691_43.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6691_47.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6691_58.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6691_62.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6691_65.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6691_66.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports the triple, as it is consistently mentioned that James Cagney starred in the movie \"Here Comes the Navy\"."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that supports the statement \"The movie 'Here Comes the Navy' stars James Cagney.\" Specifically, multiple files mention James Cagney's role in \"Here Comes the Navy,\" such as file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_6691/re-ranker-msmarco/39.txt and file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_6691/re-ranker-msmarco/57.txt."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}